previously on "desperate housewives"...
前情提要:
why on earth would you let them finger paintbefore breakfast?
（你怎么让他们没吃早饭就玩手指画）
It's my job to clean that up,so it's my call
（既然是我来管家务了，该我说了算）
Some households reversed roles
一些家庭改变了规矩
Let's give thisanother shot
（让我们再试一次吧）
Some old flames...
一些曾经的激情……
- you want me back?
-你想和我重新开始？
Yeah
是的
Were put out
消逝了
It has to be somethingyou're ingesting
（肯定是你服用了什么东西）
Who prepares your meals?
（你的三餐都是谁做的？）
I understand you've been havingsome marital problems
（据我所知，你的婚姻有些困难）
And while some learn to forgive...
而在一些人学着去原谅的时候……
deirdre got pregnantbefore I went to jail
（Deirdre在我入狱前就怀孕了）
Zach is your son,isn't he?
（Zach是你的儿子，对不对？）
Yep
（是的）
Others could not bring themselves to forget their past
另外一些人却难以忘却自己的过去
The remarkable thing about danny farrell
关于Danny Farrell众所周知的一点
was that he had only been a paperboy for six months
就是他做报童才做6个月
and in that time,he had become the enemy of every woman on wisteria lane
而就在这短短时间里，他已经成为了 Wisteria Lane所有女性的公敌
If there was a puddle on someone's property...
如果谁家的院子里有一滩水
he found it
定会被他砸中
If a new rosebush had just been planted...
如果有一丛新栽的玫瑰
he destroyed it
定会被他摧毁
If a cat was enjoying a moment in the sun...
如果是一只猫在享受日光浴
he ended it
定会被他结束
People wondered if danny would ever change
人们都在想Danny还会不会长进
They should have talked to susan mayer
如果你问Susan Mayer
She could have told them...
她会说……
obnoxious boys tend to become obnoxious men
讨厌的小子长大了就是讨厌的男人
just like the one...
就好比……
she had been married to
她嫁过的那位
Hey!
嘿！
Carl,I see you Just stop right there
Carl，我看见你了！ 给我站住
Hey,susie Q.
嘿，Susie小可爱
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
I'm justgettin' the paper
我出来取报纸
That's edie's paper and this is edie's house
这是Edie的报纸 而那是Edie房子
Do we have to do this now? I haven't had my coffee yet
我们非得现在说这个不可吗？ 我还要回去喝咖啡呢
Did you spend the nightwith edie?
你昨晚和Edie过的夜？
Oh,my god
哦，我的天
Susie,just calm down
Susie，冷静点
You are forbiddenfrom ever seeing her again.Do you hear me?Forbidden!
我禁止你再去找她，听懂了吗？ 禁止！
We're divorced You can'ttell me who I can date
我们离婚了 你不能约束我和谁约会
I live on this street Yourdaughter lives on this street
可我就住在这条街上 你女儿就住在这条街上
I will not have you flauntingyour sexcapades in front of us
我不能让你在我们面前 炫耀你那乱七八糟的私生活
- Sexcapades?
-乱七八糟的私生活？
Forbidden
禁止！
I would love to continue this but it's time for breakfast
我很乐意和你继续讨论 可现在我该吃早饭了
and edie is making mea frittata
而且Edie正在为我做肉馅蛋饼
Oh! Well,I just bet she is
哦！那…我祝她做得愉快
Mrs. Mayer,I gotta talk to you
Mayer女士，我必须和你谈谈
Oh,now is not a good time,danny
哦，现在我没时间，Danny
You're a month behindin your payments
你有一个月没交报纸钱了
I'll take care of it,I promise
我会补上的，我答应你
My dad says if you readsomething and don't pay for it
我爸爸说了 如果你享用了你没有购买的东西
that's the same as stealing
这和盗窃没有差别
Hi,ida Can we talkabout this later?
你好，Ida 我们能不能过会儿再说这个？
I just found out my exis dating my neighbor
我刚刚发现 我的前夫和我的邻居勾搭上了
and I'm really ticked off
我现在正在气头上
Save it!I provide you a service and I deserve to be paidfor that service
少来了！我给你提供了服务 而你应该为我的服务付出报酬
Yes,the women of wisteria lane believe danny farrell to be the enemy
是的，Wisteria Lane的女人们 都把Danny Farrell当作敌人……
Deadbeat!
赖帐的人！
they also believed the enemy of my enemy is my friend
她们同时也相信 敌人的敌人就是朋友
-=COSL-YTETС鹤=- sync:YTET-ronald
-=COSL-YTET小组工作室=- 翻译: 大神一郎 Milandini ethan VivienneDew 校对: 大神一郎 Milandini ethan VivienneDew 时间轴: ronald 欲乱绝情妻 第二季 第二集
Beautiful lawns...
漂亮的草坪
spacious homes...
华丽的豪宅
happy families...
幸福的家庭
these are the hallmarks of suburbia
这些都是郊区居民的特点
but if you look beneath the veneer of gracious living
但如果你仔细观察这祥和表象的背后
you will see a battle raging...
总会发现有争斗在延续……
a battle for control
为争夺控制权的争斗
You see the combatants everywhere... engaged in their routine skirmishes...
你会发现随处都有斗争者 在一切日常的冲突中……
Fighting fiercely to have dominion over the world around them
激烈的对抗 以求得对周边环境的控制
all the while knowing...
即使他们知道
it's a battle they will lose
他们肯定会输掉
Oh,hey,honey,just stick that anywhere I'll take care of it
哦，亲爱的，你可以随便放在什么地方 我会收拾的
It's really pilin' up
堆积这么多了
Oh,don't worry I have a system
哦，别担心 我自有处置方案
Really?
真的？
Yeah,every two days,I clean
是的，每两天，我打扫一次
Two days
两天
Yeah,I let the mess accumulate for two days
是的，我让这团乱麻先堆积两天
and then I clean until it's sparkling and then the cycle starts all over again
然后我再把它收拾得白净到发亮 然后整个循环继续
And why...
那怎么……
have I never seen the sparkling part?
我没看见循环中“发亮”的环节？
Well,because by the time you get home from work
因为你回家之前
the boys have messed everything up again
这些小子就把所有东西都弄乱了
See? That's what I would call a flaw in the system
瞧？这就是我所说的 方案的缺陷
What are you doin'?
你在干什么？
I think I'm asking you to clean the house
我以为我在要求你把屋子打扫干净
Really?'Cause it sounds to me like you're criticizing me
真的吗？因为在我看来 你在批评我
No
不
No,no,no,no. No
不，不，不对，没有
I'm not saying it has to be sparkling
我没有说必须要 白净到发亮
How many times did I come home to a mess and I never said a word?
多少次我回到家看见一团糟 我可没说一句话
Please,don't take this the wrong way
别，千万别误会我的意思
I think you are doing a terrific job
我觉得你的活儿干得很出色
but let's be clear When you came home,it was to clutter
但我们说明白好了 你回来的时候，家里是有些乱糟糟
I mean,come on,this is...
我是说，但是，这些……
more than that
可不只乱糟糟
Look at him,just chatting away
你看他，总是和顾客聊天
So inconsiderate
一点也不考虑后面的顾客
Phyllis,we've only been waiting here for two minutes
Phyllis，我们才等了两分钟
I told you when we left the house that I needed to eat
我们出来之前我就说了 我要吃点东西
I have low blood sugar
我有低血糖
Do you wanna see me keel over?
你想看见我厥过去吗？
No... in theory
不……理论上而言
Here you are
这是你的
Thank you
谢谢
By the way mrs.Van de kamp
顺便说一句 Van de kamp太太
I heard about your husband's passing
我听说了你丈夫的噩耗
I'm so sorry.Dr.Van de kamp was one of my favorite customers,truly
我很遗憾，Van de kamp医生 曾是我最好的顾客，真的
That's very sweet of you Thank you
你能这么说真好 谢谢你
I'm not just being polite Mrs. Van de kamp
我这么说不仅仅出于礼貌 Van de kamp太太
How are you feeling?
你现在还好吧？
Well,mr. Pashmutti...
嗯，Pashmutti先生...
we're holding up as best we can under the circumstances
就现在的情况而言，我们尽力坚持住
I'm sorry This is rex's mother,phyllis
抱歉，这位是Rex的母亲，Phyllis
I'm so sorry about your son
对于您儿子的死我感到遗憾
Thank you.You know the hardest thing is to lose a child
谢谢你，要知道 最难过的事情莫过于失去自己的孩子了
I can't even imagine
您的悲痛我很难切身体会
Come on,phyllis Let's get you something to eat
来吧，Phyllis 我们去吃点东西
We had no warning I was doing dishes when I got the call
一切都没有征兆 我接到电话的时候正在洗碗
Really?
真的？
Phyllis,there are people waiting,so come on
Phyllis，还有别人在排队呢 快走吧
Excuse me.I--I'm so sorry but my son just passed away
对不起，我很抱歉 不过我的儿子刚刚死了
Oh,I'm so sorry
哦，我很遗憾
Thank you.I mean I was telling Mr.Pashmutti here my life is--is over
谢谢，我正在和这位 Pashmutti先生说我的生活……结束了
my life is over
我的生活结束了
This is ridiculous you know that?
这荒谬极了，你知道吗？
Pen
笔
Don't you think I have better things to do than to bring you checks every day
你不觉得与其天天拿支票来给你签字 我有很多别的事要做
checks that I could be signing at home?
这些我都可以在家里签好
This one's dry
这支没墨了
You know,taking away my access to our account,that's just vindictive
让我不能动帐户里的钱 不过是你报复的手段
Thank you
谢谢
Do you knowhow long it takes me to schlep out hereto this hellhole?
你知不知道我从家里到这个烂地方 要很长时间？
Exactly. It's the only way I can guarantee you'll come and visit me
正是如此，这是唯一的办法 能保证你会来探访我
That's ridiculous.You're my husband. I love you
这很荒唐，你是我丈夫，我爱你
Obviously,I would come visit
我理所当然会来探访你
I thought it was obviousthat when you love someone you wouldn't have an affair
我曾以为你爱一个人就不会外遇是理所当然的
I was wrong,wasn't I?
我错了，不是吗？
I'm getting really tiredof this song,carlos
我有点厌倦这些老生常谈了，Carlos
Isn't it about timeyou forgave me?
应该是时候原谅我了吧
You want my forgiveness,you got it. My trust...
你要我的原谅，我给你。 你要我的信任……
that you're gonnahave to earn
那要看你的表现了
Be careful,carlos
小心点，Carlos
Up until now I've been really lonelyin that big bed of ours
到刚才为止，我在我们家那张大床上 都显得特别孤独
but when you're rude to me itmakes me wanna be not so lonely
但如果你对我不尊敬 也许我会要改善我孤独的处境
Comments like thatare exactly why you'll never againhave access to my money
这种言论正是你不准动我的钱的原因
Why are all rich men jerks?
为什么有钱的男人都那么混蛋?
The same reasonall beautiful women are bitches
你先告诉我为什么漂亮女人都那么骚
So same time tomorrow?
明天还这个时候?
Sure,baby
当然 亲爱的
What do you mean,you know?
你什么意思 你知道?
I mean,I know
我意思就是 我知道
What are you saying that your father actually told you
你说你爸跟你说过到底什么意思?
he was gonna be having a onenight stand with edie britt?
他跟edie britt玩一夜情?
Uh,mom,this wasn'ta one night stand
嗯...妈妈 这不是一夜情
He's been going out with Mrs. Britt for a few months now
他跟Britt太太已经交往了几个月了
What?
什么?
How could you not tell me that?We share everything
你怎么没告诉我? 我们之间没有秘密的
That's what we're known for That's our thing
我们一向什么事都互相分享的
Because I knew you'd wig out
我就知道你听了会激动的
Besides,haven't you always told me to respect people's privacy?
而且 你不是一直教导我要尊重别人的隐私吗?
Oh,I've neverapplied that concept to your father's sex life and you know it
噢... 我可从来没说过那包括你爸爸的私生活
Are you done?
你好了么?
No! I have not even begunripping into edie britt yet
没有! 我跟edie britt的好戏还在后头
Oh,that peroxide vulture
噢 那个贪得无厌的女人
I just know as sureas I am standing here
我就知道
that she went after your fatherjust to tick me off
她会偷偷摸摸地和你爸爸搞在一起
- Wrong again
- 你又错了
What?
什么?
He asked her out
是他约她的
You lie
你瞎说
It's true.He called her for a datesix months ago
真的 六个月前 他提出跟她约会
the day aftermy birthday party
就是我生日派对的第二天
The one at the piano bar?
在钢琴酒吧的那次?
Yeah
是的
What is it?
怎么了?
Oh,your fatherjust came over that day and told me some stuff
噢...那天你爸爸来找我 跟我说了些事情
You know,some stuffthat I haven'T...and can't tell you
那些事... 我没有...也不能告诉你
Wait. Whatever happened to"we share everything"?
等等 你不是说"我们之前没有秘密"?
Isn't that our thing what we're known for?
这就叫分享每件事情?
Um,actually,I think what we'reknown for is sharing clothes
嗯... 事实上我以为我们分享的是衣服之类的
Yeah.I thinkthat's our thing
是的 我们分享衣服
why does he keep doin' that?
他怎么不停?
He knows it's annoying
因为他知道这样很烦人
He's just tryingto get to us
他只是试图引起我们注意
Yeah,well,it's working
是啊 看来这起作用了
Knock it off,down there do you hear what I'm saying?
下面的 别再弄个不停了 听见了吗!
Matthew. Matthew!
Matthew Matthew!
Sit down
坐下
You knowwe don't talk to him
我们不能跟他说话的
That's partof his punishment
这也是对他的惩罚
How can you just sit herehour after hour and listen to that?
你怎么能听着这个 还一直坐得住?
Well,that's part of mine
这个... 是对我的惩罚
carlos,what is thisbig emergency?
carlos 什么事情那么急?
I had to cancel my hairappointment with eduardo today
害得我取消了美发预约
Baby,what is it?
亲爱的 怎么了?
I'm completelyfreaked out
我吓坏了
Why?
什么事?
There's this guy,his name's richie
这里有个叫richie的人
and he's beensaying some stuff to me
他一直骚扰我
and I'm gettin' worried
我有麻烦了
Honey,you and your macho pride
亲爱的 你的男子气呢
Just tell him you're flattered but you don't swing that way
告诉他这套不管用不就得了
He's not hitting on me you idiot,he's threatening me
他没有动手 你这个白痴 他在威胁我
Really? How?
真的? 怎么威胁?
He saidhe's gonna beat me up unless I come upwith some money
他说要是我不给钱 他就会痛扁我一顿
Well,how much money?
嗯... 要多少钱?
$7,000
- $7,000?
Keep your voice down
轻点!
Why would he thinkyou have that kind of money?
他怎么会知道你有钱?
Because yesterday in a visitingroom filled with criminals
因为昨天在接待室
my wife referred to meas a rich man
我老婆说我是有钱人 那些人渣刚好听到了
Oh,right. Sorry
噢...是啊 真抱歉
That's why I needed you to bring the checkbook
所以我叫你带上支票簿
He's actually willing to take a check?
他会收支票?
No
不是
You're gonna take the money to his girlfriend
你得把钱交给他女朋友
and if she doesn't get itby tomorrow,I'm screwed
要是明天还拿不到钱 我就完了
Honey,I thinkthis is a mistake
亲爱的 我想这样不是办法
If we give in to extortion
要是我们这次向勒索低了头
the guy's just gonna keepcoming back for more money
那人下次还会故技重演的 会勒索更多的钱
What choice do I have?
那我还能怎么办?
You're a strong guy.You went to college on an athletic scholarship,for god sakes
你很强壮 你进大学的时候还享受运动员奖学金
Yeah,it was for golf
是 但那是高尔夫
Oh
噢
You have all my pants
我裤子都在你这
Yeah,I know.Come on in
嗯...我知道 进来吧
I,uh,thought when I tookmy stuff back to my house
我...以为那次把东西已经
I got everything
通通带回去了
Oh,it's fine.They're in the garage
噢 没关系 都在车库里
So how have you been doing?
你过得怎样?
Good. Um...I'm,uh,good.
不错 嗯...我很好
I got a question for ya
我有个问题 能问吗?
Sure,what is it?
当然 什么?
- Where are we now?
- 我们现在算什么?
Where are we?
算什么?
Yeah. We're notmoving in together and we're not broken up,so where are we?
嗯 我们既没有同居 也没有分手 这算什么?
I don't know
我不知道
Since the guywho held me hostage turned out to be your son
拿我当人质的居然是你儿子
I think logic dictatesthat I should move on.
正常情况下 我不该再回头了
The problem is... I'm crazy about you
但问题是... 我是那么痴迷于你
So...
所以...
so I'm thinking we shouldkeep it casual
所以还是顺其自然吧
Casual
顺其自然
What the hell does that mean,exactly,um,casual?
顺其自然到底是怎么样?
well,I-I don't--I don't think there'sanything wrong with us
我觉得... 我们一起去看看电影
seeing a movieonce in awhile
也没什么问题
A movie. Okay.Is that it?
看电影...好吧 就这样?
Jogging?
跑步?
There's no lawagainst jogging.
跑步也不违法
Anything else?
还有呢?
Shopping. That's casual.That's fun
购物 很自然 也很有意思
Anything else we can do? Anything at all?
还有什么吗? 直接点的
brunch
早中饭吧
Brunch would be nice
来顿早中饭不错
Sounds good to me
听上去不错
All I can do is take itone day at a time.
我只能一了百了
yes
是啊
Oh,okay. Well...
噢 好的
thanks so muchfor calling.
太感谢您来电了
Who was that?
是谁?
Oh,someone namedalan hanley
一个叫alan hanley的人
My electrician?
那个电工?
Why were you on the phone sobbing to my electrician?
你向我们家电工哭诉干吗?
Oh,he called to offer youhis condolences
噢 他打来是叫你节哀顺便的的
Then why didn't youput me on?
那你怎么没让我听?
Oh,well,we got to talking and then he had to go
后来我们谈上了 然后他得走了
He--he had some very beautifulthings to say about rex
他说了rex很多好处
for god sakes,phyllis don't you ever worryabout dehydration?
上帝啊 phyllis 你就没担心过会哭得脱水?
Are you sayingthat I am too emotional?
你是说我太感情用事了?
I'm saying that even italianstake a break now and again
我是说就算情绪再激动 也需要休息
My son is dead.I'm grieving
我儿子死了 我在哀悼
So am I,but no onewould ever know it with your incessantcaterwauling
我也是 但你这样哭天喊地的也无济于事
Bree!
People want to knowhow I'm doing,but the minute they ask you
人们关心我 但他们一说起这事
you jumpinto the spotlight and they forget all about me
你就成了关注对像 然后我好像被遗忘了似的
I need consoling,too,phyllis Have you ever thought of that?
我也需要安慰的 phyllis 你有没有想过这点?
I'm sorry
抱歉
It won't happen again
不会再这样了
Thank you
谢谢
Of course,if you didn't constantlysuppress your emotions
但是 要不是你经常不把感情表露出来
people wouldn't forgetto console you
人们也不会把你遗忘
Excuse me?
你说什么?
Well,it's true You're stoicto the point of being cold
事实是 你习惯于表现得冷酷无情
I am not cold. I just--well I don't likepublic displays of emotion
我不是冷血...只是 我不习惯于在人们面前流露真情
Well,that's fine,but people wonder why they haven'tseen you cry
好吧 就算那样 但人们就奇怪怎么从没见你哭过呢
I mean,some peopleactually wonder if you truly mourn rex
我是说 有些人甚至怀疑你是不是真的为rex而哀悼
People have said that?
有人那么说?
A few,yes.
是的 有几个
Excuse me I'm looking for rita rivera.
打扰下 我在找rita rivera
Hi,are you rita?
嗨 你是rita?
Yeah,who are you?
是的 你是?
I'm,uh,I'm gabrielle solis
我...是gabrielle solis
Our--our husbands are roommatesat the prison
我们的老公是狱友
Richie and I aren't married
Richie和我可没结婚
Oh,I see. Well,uh,your boyfriend asked my husband to give this to you
噢 我明白 你男朋友叫我丈夫把这个给你
It's a sort of favor
就当是一个小忙
It's all there. $7,000
都在里面 $7,000
Son of a bitch!
狗娘养的!
Oh,don't eventhink about it
想都别想
hello...is there a problem?
有什么不对吗?
- Let me ask you a question?
- 让我问你个问题
Okay
问吧
This might seemkind of weird
可能会有点奇怪
but what do you thinkof my breasts?
但你觉得我的胸部怎么样?
Excuse me?
抱歉?
I mean,how do theylook to you?
我是说,你看它们怎么样?
they're--they're nice
它们--它们很好啊
Thank you.I like too
谢谢.我也很喜欢它们
You're right.That was weird
你说得对.是很奇怪
You have no idea what this money is for,do you?
你完全不知道这钱是要做什么的,对吧?
No.No. You--you seem to have everything you need
不知道.你看起来拥有你想要的一切
Richie wants meto get a boob job
Richie想要我去隆乳
He wants 'em bigger
他想要它们变得更大
He's obsessedwith huge breasts
他疯狂迷恋那些巨乳
So are you gonna do it?
那你要去做吗?
I told him if he came upwith the cash,I would
我跟他说如果他能拿现金来,我就做
I just never thought the moronwould actually come up with it
我怎么也没想到那蠢货居然真的拿来了
Not that it's any ofmy business but it's your body
这不关我的事,不过这是你的身体
I wouldn't change anythingunless I really wanted to
我如果不是真心想要, 是不愿改变任何部位的
But if I don't do it,he'll leave me
但是如果我不做,他就要离开我
Honey,he's in jail.How far is he gonna go?
宝贝, 他在监狱里, 他能怎样?
Maybe it's time you stood upfor yourself
也许你该力挺你自己
Tell him you don't needthe surgery
告诉他你不要做手术
It's worth a shot
值得一试
There you go.I am so proud of you
这就对了.我真为你骄傲
when lynette went back to work, she was aware her new job would be demanding
当lynette重会职场, 她知道她的新工作会很严苛
What she hadn't anticipated...
她没有预见到的是........
was the night shift
夜班
Hey,honey,I thought I heardyou come in about an hour ago
我想我一小时前就听见你回来了
I did. I had to loadthe dishwasher
没错.我得把碗放进洗碗机
You didn'thave to do that
你不必那么做的
Yeah,I sorta did
我要的
I'm sorry.I've justfallen behind on my housework
抱歉.我没做完家务活
I just had so many errandsto run today
今天有太多事要做
But I'll make up for ittomorrow,okay? I promise
明天补上,好么? 我保证
That's the beautyof my system--it's flexible
我的方法就好在这里--可通融性
You know,for the sakeof our marriage please don't mentionthe system again
为了我们的婚姻,请不要再提你的方法
I said I'm sorry
我说了我很抱歉
What in the world?
这是什么?
No,no,don't touch that Don't touch that
不,别碰!
Um,penny had a little spitty-uppy on the sheets
Penny在床单上吐了
And youdidn't change them?
你没换床单?
The towelis very clean
这毛巾很干净的
Oh,that's disgusting
真恶心
No,it's justa little spit a little milky spit upon the sheets
床单上只不过是一点口水糊糊
Please,I made a judgment call Please respect that
拜托,我已经做了决定,尊重一下巴
No,I can't respect that and do you know why?
我不能尊重,知道为什么吗?
It's stupid I'm gonna getnew sheets
太愚蠢了!我要换床单
We are not changingthe sheets
我们不换床单
Why are youyelling at me?
你为什么吼我?
I am not yelling at you and this is not about spit up
我没吼你.这已不仅仅是呕吐物的事了
Of course it is
- 当然是
No,it isn'T.It's about control
不,不是.这是关于支配权
And as you and I both know youhave some issues in this area
你我都知道你这方面有些问题
Why are you fighting so hardto sleep on baby vomit?
你为什么一定要坚持睡在小孩的呕吐物上?
I am fightingfor a principle.
我是为原则而战
Being too lazy to changethe sheets is not a principle
懒得不想换床单不是什么原则
You know what? You're not gonna win this one
你知道吗?你这次别想赢!
So you'd better justcrawl back into bed
你最好乖乖爬进床来!
and let's go to sleep
然后就让我们睡觉吧
No,tom!
别想,tom!
Tom,no! I'm gonnachange the sheets!
Tom,别想! 我要换床单!
Oh,come on!
- 噢,拜托!
No,you come on!
不,拜托你!
Just get up!Get up!
起来!起来!
That's it!All right,fine!
好啊!就这样!
Fine! Fine! Fine!
好!好!好!
Normally lynette would have spent a sleepless night
通常Lynette会度过一个不眠之夜
telling herself she didn't have control issues
告诉自己她在控制欲上没有问题
but she couldn'T
但这次她不能
She was too busy figuring out how to bend tom to her will
她忙着想法要Tom顺着她的意思来
hello?
有人吗?
Hi
Welcome to the promised land
欢迎来到欢乐乡
Go on.There
去吧,这里
Good job!
好啊!
betty?Betty?
Betty吗?
Oh,betty can I ask you a question?
噢.Betty,能问你个问题吗?
Of course.It's susan,right?
当然可以.Susan,对吧?
Yes,hi.I was just wondering,
对,我在想...
are you having some remodelingdone on your house or something?
你家在重新装修还是怎样吗?
No. Why?
没有,怎么了?
Well,I work at home
我在家工作
so I'm home a lot working
所以我经常在家
And I just keep hearingthese noises lately
最近经常听到这样的声音
it's hard to concentrate
让人很难集中精神
Well,I haven'tnoticed anything.
我什么都没注意到
Really? It sounds likeit's coming from your house.
真的?听起来是从你家传来的
You know it's likea clanging--clanging
听起来当啷当啷的
there! There that was it.Did you hear it?
听!就是这个.听见了吗?
Oh,yes Matthew's very handy
是的,Matthew很喜欢劳作
He's always doingprojects around the house
他总在家附近做东西
I guess I just don't noticethe noise anymore
我想我习惯了就不觉得有声音了
Even at 2:00 in the morning?
就算是凌晨2点?
Cause that's kind ofhard to miss
很难不听见啊
I'm so sorry
我真抱歉
Matthew is somethingof an insomniac,susan
Matthew 有失眠症,Susan
But I will talk to him and we'll put a stop to it
但我会跟他谈谈,以后不会这样了
Afternoon,Mrs. Mayer
下午好,Mayer太太
Hi,matthew
你好,Matthew
Well,it was nice chattingwith you,susan
跟你聊天真开心,Susan
This is my third phone call,mr. Flannery
这是我打的第三通电话了,Flannery先生
And if someonedoesn't call me back soon I'm going to be irritated
如果再没人回我电话,我就要生气了
Is everything all right?
一切都还好吧?
That darn insurance companyis dragging its heels
该死的保险公司在REX的赔款问题上磨磨蹭蹭 我真不懂为什么
on paying rex's policy and I don't understand why
Well,he died unexpectedly
他走的出乎意料
And that brings upa lot of questions
留下了很多问题
It's probably easier when peopleare just diseased
也许人们生病的话,还比较简单
Probably
也许
Hi
你好
- Hi
- 你好
Oh,hi,lynette
你好,lynette
I'm sorry.Am I interrupting?
抱歉,打扰到你们了吗?
No,no,not at all
不,不,没有
I saw you walk inand I've been meaning to callsince the service
我看见你进来,仪式后我就想打电话给你
but work's been so crazy so...how are you doing?
但工作忙得要死...你现在怎么样?
I'm all right
我很好
well,you look amazing
你看起来棒极了
Do I?
真的吗?
Absolutely
Absolutely 千真万确
well,I can't imaginewhat you're going through
我无法想像你正在经受怎样的痛苦
phyllis?
Phyllis?
You're going to have to stop that
你必须得停下
I can't help it
我忍不住
When people talk about rex I-I...I just get emotional
人们一谈到REX,我就伤心
Well,I'm very sorryfor your loss,too,phyllis
我也很为你难过,Phyllis
He was my firstborn
他是我的第一个孩子
I don't know what I will do without him
我真不知没了他我该怎么办
Oh,I'm so sorry
我很难过
is she gonna be okay?
她会没事吧?
yeah.Sure.Hold on a second
当然.等我一秒
there we go.Feel better?
这就对了.感觉好点了吧
Lynette,you were saying?
Lynette,你在说...?
I forgot
我忘了
That's all right It wasreally sweet of you to stop by
没关系 真是太体贴了,你过来看看我
Okay
好的
So,are we ready to order or do you needa little more time?
我们准备好点餐了, 还是再需要一点点时间?
I've been in the insuranceindustry for 15 years
我再保险业做了15年
I've never receiveda phone call like this
从来没接到过这样的电话
I'm having second thoughtsabout rex's death
关于Rex的死,我有了新的想法
I've known rex and breefor nearly 20 years
我认识Rex和Bree有20年了
And I've never hadany reason to suspect
我没有任何理由去怀疑
they were anythingbut a happy,loving couple
他们不是一对幸福相爱的夫妻
which is whythis seems so strange
奇怪的是
I found it in rex's roomafter he coded
Rex死后,我在他的病房里找到了这个
"I forgive you"?
"我宽恕你"?
George,what are youdoing here?
George,你来做什么?
I'm here to kidnap you
我来绑架你
What?
What? 什么?
Get your purse I'm gonna take you bowling
拿上你的钱包,我要带你去打保龄球
I-I don't know how to bowl
我不懂该怎么打
Or to the moviesor for a frozen yogurt Whatever you want
不然去看电影或喝瓶冰镇酸奶, 或其它你喜欢的
thank you,but I just couldn'T
谢谢,但我不 能
bree,I'm sure you haven' tgone anywhere in weeks
Bree.我肯定你已经好几周哪都没去了
You gotta get out and do things.It'll help. Trust me
你得出去做些什么.这会有帮助的.相信我
I do.I'm just...
我相信你.只是...
I'm just not ready yet
我还没准备好
But it was very sweet of youto think of me
但你能想到我,真好
Well,you know,I tried
你知道的.我试过了
And I appreciate that
我很感激
It's all right
没事的
Let it out
放轻松
You want me to die in here,don't you?
你想让我死在这,对吧?
Carlos,what happened?
Carlos,怎么了?
What do you mean "what happened?"
什么"怎么了"?
You talked rita out of taking the money
你说服Rita不要那笔钱
Is that what richie said?
Richie是那么说的吗?
Yeah,the subject came upin between kidney punches
现在他都打在我腰子上
Well,it's not my fault She didn't want the money
她不要钱不是我的错啊
Why wouldn't she want $7,000?
七千美元她怎么会不要?
Because it's for a boob job
因为这是为隆乳的
- So?
- 所以?
So her boobs are fine
她的胸本来就很美
And,honestly,what he's doing to her self-esteemis just cruel
而且,平心而论,他这么做对她太残酷了
I feel sorry for her
我真为她难过
Please,you don't care about herself-esteem any more than I do
拜托,你不比我多关心她多少
You just didn't want to give upall that money
你只是不想放弃那笔钱
Well,I do think it's sillyto give someone $7,000 if they don't want it
我是觉得把七千美元给一个 不想要的人真是太傻了
Listen to me you're gonna go back there
听着,你要回到那里
you're gonna put that moneyin rita's hands
把那笔钱放进Rita的手里
and you're gonna convince herthat life is not worth living
而且你要说服她,让她认为如果没有 一个得克萨斯州这么大的夜壶
unless she has jugsthe size of texas Do I make myself clear?
人生就白活了。我说的够清楚了吗？
I just realized rita and ihave a lot in common
我刚意识到Rita和我又很多共同点
Please don't tell me you have low self-esteem cause if I laugh now
拜托,别跟我说你们有一样低贱的自尊
I'm gonna crack the one good ribthat I have left
因为我现在一笑, 就会弄折我那根还没被打折的肋骨
We are both controlledby our husbands
我们都被丈夫支配
which is idiotic becausethey're both behind bars
这真是很傻,因为我们的丈夫都在坐牢
We should have all the power
我们应该自主
I am not tryingto control you
我不是想要支配你
I just don't wanna end upin the morgue
我只是不想最后被推进停尸间
This isn't about that
跟这个没关系
Gabrielle,the morphine's wearing off
Gabrielle,吗啡开始失效了
I really don't have timefor these games
我真的没时间跟你闹了
Me either,carlos
我也一样,Carlos
And if you expect me to go back and sweet talk herinto getting the operation
如果你期待我回去好好劝她去做手术
I can't show up empty-handed
我可不愿空手而去
Fine,bring me the checkbook I'll make out a checkfor some cash
好,拿支票本来,我开支票给你划现金
See I was thinking I'd be writing the checks
我在想由我来写支票
Gabrielle--
careful,carlos you're notin a position to argue
当心,Carlos,你根本没资格跟我争
Whoo-hoo!Susan!
呀吼!Susan!
Hey,edie
你好,Edie
- So,How much do you hate me?
- 好,你有多恨我?
What?
什么?
Oh,karl said that you know allabout our dirty little secret
噢,karl说你已经知道了我们的肮脏小秘密
- Yes,yes,I do
- 是,我知道了
Well,I feel awful
我感觉真抱歉
I should have told youthat I was doing your ex
我应该告诉你我正在搞你的前夫
Well,it would've beenthe classy thing to do
这样做了就够上等了
Well,etiquette is a lost artfor a lot of people
礼节对很多人来说都是一门消失了的艺术
You've gotta believe me,I never ever thoughtanything would happenwith us
你要相信我, 我从来没想过我们之间会发生什么
But on our first date karl took meto a mexican restaurant
但在我们第一次约会, Karl带我去了一家墨西哥餐馆
You know what I get likewhen I drink tequila
你知道我一喝龙舌兰酒就会成什么样子
A couple of shootersand my bra unhooks itself
喝了几杯后我的胸罩自动就解开了
Circumstances beyondyour control I get it.So if you'll excuse me
人没办法控制周遭环境.我明白. 麻烦你让开
Hey. Hey,hey
嘿!
I am offering youan opportunity here
我是在给你机会
I mean,go ahead--vent Let me have it
我是说,来吧!发泄啊!我该的!
Come on,tell mewhat a bitch I am
来啊,告诉我我真是一婊子
Yeah,for snacking onyour leftovers I deserve it.Come on,bring it on
没错,因为我偷吃了你的剩菜.我活该.来吧!
Honestly,edie,I don't mind
说真的,Edie,我不介意
You can skate offinto the sunset with karl Be my guest
你可以跟Karl一起溜进夕阳里.请自便
Well,that's good to know.
真高兴知道这些
I probably shouldn'ttell you this,but...
我也许不该告诉你,不过...
while we were in my jacuzzilast night...
昨晚当我们在我的极可意水流按摩浴缸里...
karl said it was the best sexhe's ever had
Karl说这是他有过的最好的性爱
bar none
毫无例外
Actually,I'm gladthat you shared that because here'sa tidbit for you
其实,我很高兴跟你分享, 因为我也有些消息要告诉你
Karl said he's stillin love with me
Karl说他还爱着我
Edie,what are you doing?
Edie,你干什么?
You are a lying liar
你是个骗人的骗子
We're in the middleof the street Would you get out of here?
我们在大街上,你离开这里好吗?
Karl never said that
Karl不会那么说的
Okay,karl asked meto get back together the day afterjulie's birthday
好的,karl在Judie的生日会后求我复合
I said no which I'm guessingis the reason
我拒绝了,而且我猜,这就是
for the now legendary tequilabra-popping incident
你那龙舌兰传奇事件的原因
Please let go
请让开
Oh,no.We're not finished here
不,我们还没完
Well,yes,we are.I'm gonna go
不,我们说完了.我要走了
You don'thave the guts
你才没胆走
In five seconds,I'm gonna punch it
5秒内,我就会踩油门
Yeah?I'll key your car!
是吗?那我就划了你的车
Not if you're suckingmy exhaust,you won'T
吸吸我的排气管,你就不会了
Take back what you said!
收回你的话
No,I won't!
我不!
Admit it,you'd do anything to destroy my happiness!
承认吧,你就是要破坏我的幸福
Edie,for god's sake
Edie,看在上帝的份上
Why would I care if you end upwith a man I despise?
我为什么要介意你跟一个 我鄙视的男人搞在一起?
Cause you and mikeare finished
因为你和Mike玩完了
Yeah,word's out
好,说出来了
And now that youcan't be happy you don't wantanyone else to be,period
因为你不高兴,你就不要任何人高兴, 经期妇女!
Edie,come back here! We're not finished yet!
Edie,回来!我们还没完!
It was an accident, Karl, Edie knows it was an accident, right?
这是个意外，Karl Eddie知道这是个意外，是么？
She knows you could have killed her.
她只知道你差点杀了她
As it is she has a shattered tibia.
事实的确如此 她胫骨粉碎了 哦，天啊 十分抱歉
Oh my god, I'm so sorry.
哦，天啊 十分抱歉 我送去了玫瑰花 她收到玫瑰了吗？
I sent roses, did she get the roses?
我送去了玫瑰花 她收到玫瑰了吗？ 收到了，但她被玫瑰刺到了
Yeah. She cut herself on the thorns
收到了，但她被玫瑰刺到了 我的天啊
Oh my god
我的天啊 你为什么跟Eddie说了我们 之间的谈话？
Why'd you tell Edie about our conversation?
你为什么跟Eddie说了我们 之间的谈话？ 是这样的，她对和你上床感到 很满足
She was gloating about sleeping with you, and I just wanted to shut her up
是这样的，她对和你上床感到 很满足 我只是想让她闭嘴
- Oh, so you were jealous? - No!
这么说你嫉妒了？ 不，没有
No!
不，没有
it's we were married,
只是我们曾经是夫妻
and she is trying to make this **** little affair you guys have going on part with that and I just...I got mad
只是我们曾经是夫妻 而她却要把你们的这点小事情 和我们的过去混为一谈 这实在是... 我有点发火了
Susan, you remember the morning you saw me with Edie's paper?
Susan, 你还记得你看到我 捡Eddie的报纸的那个早晨吗？ 在那前一天晚上，我问了她 是否愿意同居
It was the night before I asked her if she'd like to live together. And she said yes
在那前一天晚上，我问了她 是否愿意同居 她回答说“是”
Susan.
Susan？ 你让我安静下 干脆让上帝把我杀了好了
Just give me a moment, I'm asking god to kill me.
你让我安静下 干脆让上帝把我杀了好了
Look, she's fine, she goes with the flow...you know at this time in my life I need that
别这样，她不是很好么 她只是做了个顺水人情 你也知道在这种时候 我需要它
Are you in love with her?
你...爱上她了？ 如果我说“是”你会介意吗？
Would you care if I were?
如果我说“是”你会介意吗？
I want you to be happy
我希望看到你快乐 我甚至有点希望看到Eddie快乐
I even sort of want Edie to be happy
我希望看到你快乐 我甚至有点希望看到Eddie快乐 但是？
I want to be happy first
但是？ 我自己要先得到快乐 Mike本来要搬来和我一起住的
Mike and I were supposed to move in together, you know...this was supposed to be my time
Mike本来要搬来和我一起住的 这一切本该属于我！
I heard you and the plumber were having your problems. Is it over?
我听说了你和水管工之间 出问题了 你们...玩完了吗？
I don't know.
不知道
It's truly complicated.
不好说
So you never answer my question. Are you in love with her?
你还没回答我的问题呢 你爱上她了？
I don't know.
我不知道
I promise you this much:
但是我敢向你保证： 我从未像爱你那样去爱别的女人
I'll never love another woman the way I loved you
You walked out on me.
别忘了你把我甩了！
Yeah...but look how far. I'm just up the street
是啊，但是你看看我才跑了多远？ 我就在街那头
Mommy mommy thank god you are home
妈咪妈咪，终于把你盼回来了 嘿，宝贝
Hey Sweetie! Why? What's wrong?
嘿，宝贝 怎么了，出什么事了？
Daddy found a rat
爸爸发现了一只老鼠
Oh...Did he now?
哇，这下麻烦大了
Honey?
宝贝
I'm home
我回来了
It was good. But more important how was yours?
很好，但更重要的是—— 你过得如何？
Hey babe!
嘿，宝贝
Hi
- Hi
- Hi, How was your day?
- Hi，你今天过的怎么样？
- Parker told you about the rat, uh?
Park跟你说了老鼠的事情是吧？
Yep.
是啊
Oh my god it was so disgusting
见鬼了，真是恶心
I can't understand. And there was sitting on the counter eating the leftover goachy sandwich.
我才下楼，就看见那只老鼠 它坐在柜台上， 吃着一块剩下的奶酪三明治
The sandwiches from yesterday?
昨天我们吃的那些三明治？ 是的，没错，我知道这房子 的确显得非常乱
OK, yes, the house has been too messy, obviously my system has some kinks in it,
是的，没错，我知道这房子 的确显得非常乱 我的系统出了点问题 但是，你看看
but check it out, I got my act together
我的系统出了点问题 但是，你看看 我现在全都搞定了 哇，那么，我帮你把老鼠拿出去吧
so I take it you took the rat outside?
哇，那么，我帮你把老鼠拿出去吧
Oh no , I smashed it with a shovel
哇，那么，我帮你把老鼠拿出去吧 哦，不用了，我用铲子把它砸扁了
You killed it?
你杀了它？
not on the first blow
我只是打了它一下而已 唔，真恶心
disgusting!
唔，真恶心
Hey
嘿，小家伙 我对于发生的一切感到十分抱歉
little guy
I just wanted to say I'm really sorry about what happened
嘿，小家伙 我对于发生的一切感到十分抱歉 尤其是那铲子 其实我并不想那样的
with the shovel.
尤其是那铲子 其实我并不想那样的
neither one of us saw that coming...
I know it's not much consolation, but you really helped my marriage.
我知道这么说好像起不到什么安慰作用 但是你确实挽救了我的婚姻
That's a lot for a little rat to accomplish in one lifetime
你真是生的伟大，死的光荣啊
Well, it's getting late so...
好像也挺晚了，那么...
hats off to ya.
入土安息吧
So you'd say the abuse starteda few years into your marriage?
你是说虐待在你们结婚几年后就发生了？
It started so slowly I didn't realizewhat was happening
开始只是一些小事情 我没有意识到有什么隐情
I mean,he'd slap meover some little problem
比如说，他会由于一个小问题 而打我一个耳光
But he'd always apologize
但是他总是会道歉
Then it got worse
然后事情变糟了
And one day,eight years ago my sonspilled soda on our new carpet
然后在8年前的一天 我的儿子把苏打水洒到了新买的地毯上
Before I could moveto protect him
在我反应过来之前
virgil had knocked himon the ground and began kicking him
Virgil就已经把儿子打倒在地 并且不断的踢他
I wanted to protect my baby but I didn't get there in time
我想去保护孩子 可是我没来得及
What happened to your son?
你儿子怎么了？
Well,he died
呃，他死了
I came across one ofhis baby pictures last weekend
上周末我偶然翻到他的相片
That's when the nightmaresstarted again
然后我又开始做恶梦了
The last doctor I saw said thatI needed to let go of my guilt
上一个医生说我需要 对我的过失释怀
and then I wouldstart sleeping again
然后我就能够安稳睡觉了
Of course that's easier saidthan done
当然说总是比做容易
And I am getting so tired
我现在感到身心俱疲
I'm gonna start youon nitrazepam
我先给你开个硝基安定 （镇定药）
That shoulddo the trick
应该会有些效果
Thank you
谢谢
I certainly hope your husbandwas punished for what he did
我真希望你的丈夫恶有恶报
Oh,there was retribution
来世会有报应的
I made sure of that
我确信这一点
Where are youoff to?
你去做什么？
I'm,I'm going to seerex's lawyer
我，我要去见Rex的律师
We're going to go over somedetails involving rex's will
我们要商谈一下Rex的遗愿的问题
Phyllis...
obviously,I'm just mortifiedover slapping you
显然，我因为掴你而感到羞怒
I've--I've just been ina weird place since rex's death,but...
Rex去世以后我就处在一种 莫名奇妙的状态中，但是...
that's no excuse
我还是没有理由那么做
I'm very,very sorry
我十分，十分的抱歉
No need to apologize
你不需要道歉了
You're family All's forgiven
我们是一家人嘛 有什么不好说的
Really?
真的？
It's been a difficult timefor all of us
对我们来说 这都是一段难熬的时光
I totally understand
我完全理解
Now,go
快去吧
You don't want to be late foryour meeting about rex's will
你一定不想迟到那个关于Rex的遗愿的 会议吧
Claims.This is joe flannery
你好，我是Joe Flannery
Hello,could I speak to someone about the death benefits for rex van de kamp,please?
你好，我要找负责处理 Rex Van de Kamp的后事的那个人
This is his mother
我是他的妈妈
Yes,we've already spokento his wife several times
是的，我们已经和他的妻子说过很多次了
We are moving as quicklyas we can
我们在尽快的进行处理
Are you aware that mydaughter-in-law has a boyfriend?
你知道我的儿媳有个男友吗？
I'm listening
我记一下
Control--
控制——
it's extraordinary the tactics people employ to obtain it
人们为了得到它真是无所不为
Some rely on deception
有些人靠诡计
While others engage in outright trickery
有的人则用正直的把戏
Then there are those who resort to extortion
还有一些人则屈服于勒索
Why do we fight so hard for control?
我们为什么这么拚命的希望得到控制呢？
because we know to lose it
因为我们知道，一旦失去了控制
is to put our fate in the hands of others
我们的命运就掌握在别人手里了
And what could be more dangerous?
还有什么比这更危险的呢？